[Music]
[Música]
Well let's see family today I was going to watch a
bueno a ver familia hoy iba a ver un
Nauta video not for nothing but
vídeo de nauta porque no por nada sino
because it encompasses the
porque engloba el tema del que quiero
topic I want to talk about and well the video turbo plan we don't get in you're talking about the last money that turbo plan those two entrances to which highway are they going to take by ass [ __ ] okay these are not entrances in the shape of my head and I would like you in this hair that they don't
quisiera tú te en este pelo que no se
fall out and one says move every summer okay do
caen y uno dice mueve cada verano vale
n't worry if one day the
no te preocupes que si algún día las
entrances grow don't worry I'm going
entradas crecen no te preocupes que voy
to Turkey paint or solve in a
a turquía pintar o solucionar en un
moment no no to press anyone for
momento no no a pulsáis a nadie de
crimes because let's try laws I don't
delitos porque lo intentemos de leyes no
know if that could be cover up or I don't know
sé si eso podría ser encubrir o no lo sé
really I don't know the truth what is
de verdad no lo sé la verdad lo que sí
clear to me is that it has been kept quiet
tengo claro es que se le ha callado
for months it has been quiet for
durante meses se ha callado durante
months and used it why man you can't
meses y la utilizado por qué tío tú no
take it is another year very clear
puedes [__] es otro año clarísimo
you can't take and use that but
tú no puedes [__] y utilizar eso pero
well let's let the law do what it has to do
bueno ya dejémoslo que la ley haga lo
okay
que tenga que hacer vale
[Music]
[Música]
the turbo plas
el turbo plas
it seems that turbo plan and fact that they
parece ser que turbo plan y hecho que le
told him the other day  they are insulting
dijeron el otro día nos están insultando
the sal seo channels that we do
a los canales de sal seo que hacemos
live okay for having for having
directos vale por haber por haber
said that he had a plan
por haber dicho que tuvo plan os
we informed you let's see the other day we were
informábamos a ver el otro día estuvimos
talking about this topic not the silver topic the
hablando este tema no el tema silver la
scam that they have done to him
estafa que le han hecho
[Music]
[Música]
and that turbo plugins a video accusing
y que turbo plugins un video acusándolo
him of being a scammer okay we were
de estafador a él vale lo estuvimos
watching it as you see it is absurd to accuse
viendo como ves es absurdo acusar a
silver of scams very absurd look I
silver de estafas muy absurdo mira yo
think about these things the same as we
pienso en estas cosas lo mismo que we
live you may like the ene efe that you may not
live te pueden gustar los ene efe que no
like you may think that the
te pueden gustar te puede parecer que el
guy is stupid because he is stupid he is
tío tonto porque es que es tonto él
useful like this it is seen that for many years on the
sirve de este se ve que muchos años en
internet he does not have as much trust
internet no lleva como elevada confianza
in a guy who does not even know his name or
a un tío que no sabe ni su nombre ni
have his information and you are going to leave him
tiene sus datos y le vas a dejar de
as you are going to leave him as you
confianza como le vas a dejar de
trust a portfolio of 160 thousand bucks
confianza una cartera de 160 mil pavos
in solana
en solana
way how he is going to get involved now
manera como se va a meter sirve ahora
with the collaborations that he is doing
con las colaboraciones que está haciendo
with the brand with the important youtuber and
con marca con los youtuber importante y
all that in tarnishing his image by scamming his
todo eso en manchar su imagen estafando
followers and why is he going to scam
a los seguidores y para qué va a estafar
160 thousand dollars when silver
160 mil dólares cuando esos silver lo
earns that in two or three months
gana en dos o tres meses
this is absurd  of the people who accuse
es absurdo esto de la gente que acusa
this fable and mobile network and with the
esta fábula y red móvil y con los
millions and millions and millions that they
millones y millones y millones que
have it is not enough for anyone to like
tienen no basta para nadie que te gusten
bad nfc that you trust them it is not worth
malas nfc que confíes en ellos no vale
great let's see the video here
estupendo vamos a ver el vídeo por aquí
here I came
aquí
back to see that they are vtv like a
he vuelto al ver que son vtv como una
kind of virtual youtube that is like it
especie de virtual youtube que es como
makes videos but with the
que hace vídeos pero con las gafas del
oculus rif glasses and its movements are
oculus rif y sus movimientos se
transferred, let's understand that in the
trasladan vamos entiendo yo que en los
monkeys that it makes they are transferred to the
monitos que hace se trasladan al
little doll the fact is that this kid I
muñequito el caso es que este chaval lo
was your see in fact he is
estuve tu ver de hecho es que se está
becoming very famous now I think he is
haciendo famosísimo ahora creo que está
even making videos with the blond and
haciendo vídeos incluso con el rubios y
with Greece he is making videos like
con de grecia está haciendo vídeos como
with the greats and see the closest thing to
con los grandes y ver lo más parecido a
a talking tumor that I have seen in a long
un tumor parlante que he visto en mucho
time more tumor than tumor cited since
tiempo más tumor que tumor citó ya que
from there you imagine your little love made
de ahí os imagináis a tu amorcito hecho
by two see hey maybe it is not a bad idea
by two ver oye igual no es mala idea
at all that the little animal or whatever the [ __ ] is
total que el animalito o lo que [__] sea
the experiment I saw it the other day
el experimento yo lo vi el otro día tío
well man the other day I did not see it for a
bueno el otro día no lo visto hace
long time in a video that biden out the one that he
tiempo en un vídeo que biden out el que
used for a while as a  crazy
utilizó por un tiempo como un loquendo
but super good a person really appears
pero súper bueno se aparece una persona
and it's like [ __ ]
y es como [__]
these visits have gone well as
que le ha ido bien a estas visitas como
if nothing or I mean like [ __ ] for people it doesn't
si nada o sea como [__] por la gente no
bother them listening I
la molesta escuchaba yo
would have created myself no longer because
me hubiera creado ya no porque ya me
other worlds already know me but I would have
conoce otros mundos pero yo me hubiera
created channels like that a channel like that with
creado canales así un canal así con
Julian if you don't use your face you don't use a
julian si no utilizas tu cara no utiliza
tube you use your tone of you they make you
tubo lo utiliza tu tono de tu hacen
titled it
titulada
seems like a total boreal because that way nobody
parece una boreal total pues así nadie
knows you take it by the ass past your
te conoce a tomar por culo pasado tu
opinion news your things and without putting
opinión noticia tus cosas y sin meterte
absolutely anything into it
absolutamente nada
I believed that in a person I and
yo me creía que en una persona yo me y
a person of how hard it has been done
una persona de lo duro que se ha hecho
an off project I had never heard of it I
un proyecto en off no lo había escuchado
thought that the light and everything goes to
nunca pensé que la luz y todo se da a la
hell what a shame shame shame' I'm asking
[__] que pena penita pena' voy pidiendo
now the psychologist is there and the day that they are
ahora está el psicólogo y el día que se
all sold suddenly all
venden todos de repente desaparece todo
the money disappears disappears in all the nfc
el dinero desaparece en todos los nfc
because obviously in case
porque ya obviamente por si desaparece
the money disappears and the website and everything no well
el dinero y la página web y todo no pues
the beings are no longer worth anything and suddenly it's
los seres ya no valen nada y de repente
like oh they robbed me today is not the
es como ay me han robado hoy no es el
best of days since it is not the
mejor de los días ya que no es el
launch that we were waiting for the
lanzamiento que estábamos esperando el
programmer who worked with us
programador que trabajó con nosotros
decided to steal absolutely everything
decidió robar absolutamente todo lo
raised in  the mountain or the rats and
recaudado en el monte o de las ratas y
defrauded other projects in which he
defraudó a otros proyectos en los que
was involved such that I had a plan for
estaba involucrado tal que tuve plan a
the figurine hey speaking of figurine 7
la figurita oye hablando de figurita 7
that open had a funk or pop I
que abren tuviera un funk o pop me lo
bought it in I accused him directly of the
comprada en lo acusé directamente del
hunter but people on the other hand this
cazador pero la gente en cambio este
youtube which is a youtube the big but
youtube que es un youtube el grande pero
very big bear has more than a billion it
muy grande osa tiene más de un billón de
has almost two million followers
se tiene casi dos millones de seguidores
on youtube and more than a million
en youtube y más de un millón de
followers on twitter has scammed more than
seguidores en twitter ha estafado más de
160 thousand euros from its followers literally right
160 mil euros a sus seguidores literal
in front of their faces because the scam for the
por toda la cara pues que la estafa para
thing scams right in front of their faces I had not
que la cosa estafa por la cara no había
seen the impressive video it is ten
visto el vídeo impresionante es diez
times worse button than ten times a hundred
veces peor botón que diez veces cien
times worse than what willy could have done
veces peor que lo que ha podido hacer
and it also leaves open the possibility that
y también deja abierta la posibilidad de
the keychain was very innocent or
que el llavero haya sido muy inocente o
half mongolian or go look or you are very
medio mongol o vaya mira o eres muy
stupid or you are lying not to try to
tonto o estás mintiendo no para intentar
sneak away and you did all this scam
como escabullirse y toda esta estafa la
because if not I do not understand
has hecho tú porque si no no lo entiendo
because of course you are a genius at
porque desde luego que eres un genio de
scamming and now you are cheating with the
la estafa y ahora estás engañando con el
world it is quite quite short like
mundo es bastante bastante cortito como
ambiguous that only says as if saying that  you
ambiguo que solo dice como diciendo que
are nobody you are so stupid for that the
no eres nadie es tan tonto para eso lo
next thing since we have seen that he did
siguiente ya que hemos visto que sí que
accuse him directly giving a cocktail it is
le acusó directamente dando un cóctel es
a possibility that
una posibilidad que
this whole scam from the beginning but
toda esta estafa desde el principio pero
I do not assure at any time that he
yo no asegura en ningún momento que él
took and orchestrated all of this from the
cogiera y orquestra todo esto desde el
beginning the way they have could have been
principio la forma han podido ser un
somewhat murky the very clumsy but the fact
tanto turbia el muy torpe pero el caso
is that no matter how many indications there are he cannot be
es que por mucho indicio que haya no se
directly accused I think we
le puede acusar directamente eso creo
have that clear not basically from
que lo tenemos claro no básicamente por
what we have said many times on this
lo que hemos dicho muchas veces en este
channel justice has not yet spoken
canal la justicia todavía no ha hablado
they entrust 160 thousand dollars to a person
le confían 160 mil dólares a una persona
that you do not know who it is but a kid from
que no sabes quién es pero un chavo de
Reuters from a project decided to take
reuters de proyecto decidió llevarse
all the money he took it a complete success
todo el dinero se lo llevó todo un éxito
and not only that but you give him access to
y no sólo eso sino que le das acceso a
the cryptocurrency wallet in which
la cartera de cripto monedas en la que
those 160 thousand dollars are and you give
están esos 160 mil dólares y tú le das
access to a person that you do not know at
acceso a una persona que no conoces de
all
nada
as you have heard the homunculus of the
como habéis escuchado el homúnculo del
design where they carry that never came to
diseño donde llevan que jamás salió a la
light says that the scammed was him we already
luz dice que el estafado fue el ya
know a little more about the person we
sabemos más un poquito más de la persona
already know his name we already know what he is
ya sabemos su nombre ya sabemos cuál
such let's go that they did not know the name
está tal vamos que no sabían el nombre
of the person with  that I didn't even know the
de la persona con la que no sabía ni el
name he gave that they were working with
nombre dio a que estaban trabajando
until later, that is, until the
hasta después o sea hasta que el
investigator found out, I know that they were
investigador lo averiguado sé que
working with a person whose
estaban trabajando con una persona que
name they didn't know and what led
no sabían su nombre y en que desemboque
to all this, well, the
a todo esto pues en que la marioneta
virtual puppet said that he was going to shove a
virtual ha dicho que le va a meter un
stick up Turbo Poder's judicial ass. He
palito por el culo judicial a turbo
said today and threatened me
poder ha dicho hoy y me ha amenazado
like he was going to report me, that is,
como como que me voy a denunciar o sea
I didn't expect this at all. They
esto ya yo no me lo esperaba para nada
say I'll send you a report that they'll
que dicen te mando un reporte al que te
screw you x2. It's true that they won't
ching x2 es verdad con lo que no te
stop monetizing you. You have to be careful.
dejan de monetizar hay que tener cuidado
It's true. I spoke with Enrique about those
es verdad hablé con enrique sobre esos
10, true. True. How do you upload videos that we
10 verdad verdad como subas vídeos con
don't give you on the channel? It's true.
lo que no te demos en el canal es verdad
Damn, I could have had a bad time.
[__] podría haber tenido un marrón
Authors,
autores
for tomorrow, I'll take advantage of it. Tomorrow I'll take advantage of it. Yes,
para mañana provecho mañana aprovechó sí
yes, I can file a lawsuit against Chavo who
sí puedo meter una demanda de chavo que
was defaming me, but
me estaba difamando pero
tomorrow I'll take advantage of it. If the
y mañana aprovechó si le mete una el
guy who is defaming me files one against Turbo
chavo que me está difamando al turbo
Plan, but well, Turbo supports us with this
plan pero bueno turbo apoya con este
type of thing, we don't have to be
tipo de cosas tampoco tenemos que
scared, you're used to it, do
asustarnos tú tienes está acostumbrado
you remember what happened to you with Wind and I didn't
te acuerdas lo que te pasó con wind y no
they found out and I got this letter and
lo averiguaron y me llegó esta carta y
basically what it is is like a
básicamente lo que es es como una
threat when wind and sent us this
amenaza cuando wind y nos mandó esta
threat telling me that if I don't delete
amenaza diciéndome que si yo no borro
all the videos eyes of all the
todos los vídeos ojos de todos los
videos the queue and when to wind and
vídeos la cola y cuando a wind y nos
sent us that but it's that he sent it to me
mandó eso pero es que a mí me lo mandó
too like but what have I told
también como pero yo que te he dicho a
you and to have I will delete it that I have
ti y para tener yo lo borrara que tengo
about wind and get is going to report me and
sobre wind y get me va a denunciar y
now comes the icing on the cake I
ahora viene la guinda del pastel yo le
will be happy he will not give it in fact he will sign
alegrará no lo dará de hecho él signará
video in his video okay lately I don't even
vídeo en su vídeo vale últimamente no
have time to blink
tengo tiempo ni para pestañear por lo
therefore I have not been seeing any
tanto no he estado viendo ninguna
criticism or any opinion on this subject
crítica ni ninguna opinión de este tema
but pay attention to what turbo pija says here
pero atención a lo que dice aquí turbo
then take into account the issue of the
pija luego en cuenta el tema de los
salt channels whether or not they have talked
canales de sal se o no que han hablado
about this subject I have not seen several channels
de este tema no he visto varios canales
you know that it is I do not even know why
de sabéis que está no sé ni por qué
turbo plan ran and put us here to give our
turbo plan corrió y nos metió aquí a
opinion on what we had said the
opinar sobre lo que habíamos dicho los
channels to be like that more strange that they
canales al ser como que más raro que
have said the channels to the seo
hayan dicho los canales al seo
or rather that they have talked about this subject and
o sea que han hablado sobre este tema y
that most of them like my videos are
que la mayoría de ellos como mis vídeos
not on twitter well they have  added to the
no hay en twitter pues se han sumado al
genoa and throwing [ __ ] at me many of them
genoa y a tirarme [__] muchos de ellos
saying well using me as
diciendo pues que sirviéndose de mí como
if I don't inform myself no how have I made my
que no me informo no como he hecho mi
video without informing myself at all
vídeo sin informarme absolutamente nada
let's see is that sincerely if we already
vamos a ver es que sinceramente si ya
had at the height that the turbo
teníamos a la altura que sube el turbo
plan goes up we already have the videos of the other we already
plan ya tenemos los vídeos del otro ya
have the videos of the other saying that
tenemos los vídeos del otro diciendo que
he was going to refill the money in
él iba a volver a rellenar el dinero en
the account he and the team was going to
la cuenta él y el equipo iba a volver a
refill the money a guy who earns those
rellenar el dinero un tío que gana esos
two or three months
dos o tres meses
well the truth is that if you had
pues la verdad que si tuvieras informa
a little more information and based on the indications
un poco más y ya en base a los indicios
that we have had on other occasions with
que hemos tenido en otras ocasiones con
turbo plan well it was not very bad either I do
turbo plan pues tampoco fue muy mala yo
not remember what I said I think
no me acuerdo que lo que dije yo creo
I laughed and little more I
que me reí y poco más yo pasé muy de
tiptoed with this subject it is
puntillas con este tema
very funny to me that they take and
me hace muchísima gracia que cojan y se
join the fashion of telling me that I did not
unan a la moda de decirme que no me
inform myself all these youtubers of salt
informó todos estos youtubers de sal se
or that they take literally and record their
o que cogen literalmente y graban sus
videos live they do not take read four
vídeos en directo no cogen leen cuatro
tweets per ence and it does not move you little the
tweets por ence y no te mueve poco el
salsero and track no and they tell me that he did
salsero y pista no y me dicen a mí que
not train me when I am
no me formó cuando soy
this was as if it
esto fue como
were  what does it matter that each because this
que sea que importa que cada porque esto
is or he his brother the cake am I I
es o él su hermano el tarta soy yo yo
think that more than anything he goes for him he stutters
creo que más que nada va por él tartaja
because because he treats like this he was more
porque porque él trata así fue más
forceful and more against him we
contundente y más contra él nosotros
read a little of what he was saying
leímos un poco lo que fue diciendo
we not the south I did not see it but
nosotros yo no el sur no lo vi pero yo
what we did here was more or less what
lo que hicimos aquí fue más o menos lo
some and others put
que los puso unos y otros
and little more is
y poco más
worth I do not know how many I think we are going for
vale no sé cuántos yo creo que vamos por
him he stutters I do not know what the pimp said
él tartaja no sé lo que dijo el chulo
but it is like well the problem is that
pero es como bueno que el problema en
we make the live content
que nosotros hagamos el contenido en
like almost the majority of youtubers
como casi la mayoría de youtuber de hoy
today the majority of youtube today
en día la mayoría de youtube hoy en día
have live content because it is
se han contenido en directo porque es
a waste of time and money they make
una pérdida de tiempo y de dinero hacen
the videos or I mean I do not put myself in here
los vídeos o sea yo no me pongo en aquí
you have hours recorded a video send it
tenéis horas ha grabado un vídeo mandar
to the editor the editor edits it I do not know
al editor del editor lo edite no sé
how much and then charge less or the
cuánto para luego cobrar menos o lo
same as doing the live I do it
mismo que haciendo los directos lo hago
live I am earning money
en directo estoy ganando dinero en
live and then I upload it that nvidia
directo y luego lo subo que nvidia
30,000 visits per train also visits
30.000 visitas por tren también visitas
that you catch me 50 for 50 days and in 1,000
que me pillas 50 por 50 días y en 1.000
6,000 because I've already used the content
por 6.000 porque yo ya el contenido ya
live and I'm already
lo he aprovechado en directo y ya les
using it here you understand me
aprovecho aquí me entienden
but there's something wrong
pero algo que tiene de malo
with you being here to watch the
que tú lo te pongas aquí a ver los
videos live and comments since it's
vídeos en directo ya comentarios al ser
live you
directo
comment on it live not like the
lo comentas en directo ya no como el
rest of the people I'm the one who takes it
resto de personas yo el que coge
investigates and tries to go a little further
investiga e intenta ir un poco más allá
and criticize those of us who are
y hacer las críticas a los que estamos
here I speak for myself for example I
aquí yo hablo por mí yo por ejemplo
investigate a lot about the videos that I'm
investigo muchísimo sobre los vídeos que
going to make but a lot a lot
voy a hacer pero muchísimo muchísimo tal
maybe now there are topics that are very banal there
vez ahora hay temas que son muy banales
are topics that are inherited nonsense has
hay temas que son chorradas heredadas ha
said I don't know who from the other wing said has
dicho no sé quién del otro wing dicho ha
posted a tweet web I will do has posted a
puesto un tweet web me haré ha puesto un
line I don't know where
line no sé dónde
or I'll just comment thank you thank you very much
o simplemente te comento gracias muchas
king remind everyone that tomorrow
gracias rey recordar a todos que mañana
at one o'clock at night
a la una de la una de la noche
sur and I will be with Frank Cuesta in
sur y yo estaremos con frank cuesta en
the live on the France Cuesta channel
el directo en el canal france cuesta
but well we will be here and we
pero bueno estaremos aquí y lo
will send it there but what he tells you I
mandaremos para allá pero él lo que os
precisely inform myself gossip and
yo precisamente me informo chismosa y
banal topics that you don't need an
temas banales de lo que no necesitas una
investigation of the voice of the host
investigación de la voz de la [__]
I think that there are I think that there are topics in
yo creo que hay yo creo que hay temas en
those who did not need to investigate here
los que no necesitaban investigar aquí
people like me and the south we have been very
gente como yo y el sur pasamos muy
low profile lately it is not
con el perfil bajo últimamente no merece
worth getting into trouble with
la pena meterte en problemas con la
people getting along badly with people be I
gente llevarte mal con la gente sea yo
am here commenting he goes out often I say
estoy aquí comentó el sal seguido digo
what I think without disrespecting
lo que opino sin faltarle el respeto a
anyone and I have no reason to start a
nadie y no tengo por qué inicia una
war or a battle against anyone or
guerra ni una batalla contra nadie ni
go personal here in the end we are here
que vaya a lo personal aquí al fin
to earn as much money as
estamos para ganar el máximo de dinero
possible and making the
posible y rentabilizando el tiempo lo
most of the time as possible
máximo posible
contributing working and other things no longer
cotizando trabajando y otras cosas ya no
half takes an issue the personal I have no
media toma un tema lo personal no tengo
desire for more people to sue me if
más ganas de que más gente me demande si
someone wants to sue me for the rest
alguien me quiere demandar por lo demás
remedy because they will sue it is understood
remedio porque demandará se entiende
but if I can avoid problems and the
pero si puedo evitar problemas y cuantos
fewer problems the less bad vibes and the
menos problemas cuando menos mal rollo y
salsero is commenting or I mean I
está comentando el salsero o sea yo
can for example they are fighting now a
puedo por ejemplo se pelean ahora un
play with rebound I can comment that the
play con rebote yo puedo comentar que el
salsero did not disrespect either of the
salsero no le faltó respeto a ninguno de
two neither of them gets angry
los dos ninguno de los dos se enfada
with me hey well in this I think he is
conmigo oye pues yo en esta creo que aún
not right yet hey well I think that in
no tiene razón oye pues yo creo que en
this network he is wrong and if I were a
esta red está equivocado y yo si fuera
bombo I would have used another
rebombo hubiera depto utilizado otra
way of acting is to meditate you can
forma de actuar es meditar lo puede
say with respect
decir con respeto
and that is not the sup support and it is
y eso no es el sup apoyan y es
simply that I am not going to take anyone out and
simplemente que no voy a sacar a nadie y
have them all against each other or anything I
tenerlos a todos en contra ni nada
prefer
prefiero
men
hombres
because I have repeated a strike but as
porque he repetido un strike pero a
time goes by it will pass us that you have
pasar tiempo se va a pasarnos que os he
coincided two or three times with him we have
coincidido dos o tres veces con él nos
made a couple of good
hemos hecho un par de chistes de buena
internal jokes and now you also think helping
interna y ahora también crees ayudando a
frank account for dispute mother understands
frank cuenta por disputa madre entiende
beyond commenting the salsero
más allá de comentar el salsero por
above and measure me that he did not inform me
encima y medir a mí que no me informó
when they take them and read four tweets
cuando cogen ellos y leen cuatro tweets
and ccoo and I am preparing the
y ccoo y yo me estoy preparando los
videos several days before it is that in the end
vídeos varios días antes es que al fin a
another plant prepares several days of video
otra planta prepara varios días de vídeo
its king and on top of that the algae involved if
su rey y encima las algas metido si es
in the end what people want is to
que al final la gente lo que quiere es
find out about salt often there are people who
enterarse de sal seguido hay gente que
like blood but they are
les gusta la sangre pero es la gente
super toxic people cunningly when maybe
súper tóxica astutamente cuando a lo
the pathetic channels make the
mejor los canales penosos me hacen los
videos for me the pathetic channels and you go to
vídeos los canales penosos y te vas a
elsa now and the scare savioli dick
elsa ya y el susto savioli [__] la
darla's pet the dog are
mascota de darla el perro son gente
toxic people it is that the aces
tóxica es que los as
and in the end most people what they
y al final la mayoría de gente lo que
want are the followers they have for
quiere son los seguidores que tiene por
example cal  from peredo without half tuberos
ejemplo cal de peredo sin medio tuberos
and people like that
y gente así
find out about the move uy michu has
enterarse de la movida uy michu lo ha
said it the whole gala happy with this
dicho toda la gala contenta con esto
posted I have done dallas and if anything a
puesto lo he hecho dallas y si acaso una
very superficial opinion I this it too
opinión muy por encima yo esto lo
much I this would not have said yes
demasiado yo esto no hubiera dicho yo sí
and out and out has commented the sanse or to
y fuera y fuera ha comentado el sanse oa
inform people
informar la gente
and it was like why do you want to get involved you
y fue de a para qué quieres meterte tú
are the protagonist see you later it is
eres el protagonista hasta luego se
understood it
entiende
depends it depends on some topics that do not
depende depende en algunos temas que no
affect you more the colors can be more
te toque más los colores pueden ser más
incisive but incisive but there are topics
incisivos pero incisivo pero hay temas
that are very banal since Greece has
que son muy banales ya que grecia tiene
a problem
un peo
because I wanted to investigate the
porque quería investigar el dióxido de
carbon dioxide that it has that will have a
carbono que tiene eso tendrá un dióxido
carbon dioxide that you [ __ ] and we have never
de carbono que te cagas y nunca hemos
said
dicho
finally he wants to enter from sanse and
finalmente quiere entrar del sanse y
practice it quickly and out from
practicarlo rápido y fuera desde
doing what they have or taking and being
hacerles lo que tienen o [__] y ser
some [ __ ] suckers directly from the
unos chupan pollas directamente de los
big youtubers instead of trying to be
youtubers grandes en lugar de intentar
a little critical sucking [ __ ]
ser un poco críticos chupar la [__] no
is not not being critical sucking the buoys that you do
es no ser crítico chupar las boyas que
not take and say oh auron it is that you are the
no cojas y diga ay auron es que eres el
best hair there is now is that this is never
mejor pelo hay ahora es que esto nunca
wrong your videos are the best
se equivoca tus vídeos son los mejores
how good the quality of your  camera man I
que buena la calidad de tu cámara tío me
love how he does it it's more fun you
encanta como lo hace es más divertido
're the best you never make a mistake
eres el mejor tú nunca te equivoca
campillo smoking live but the
campillo fumando en directo pero el
cigar that you grab the best in the world
cigarro que tú coges el mejor del mundo
sucking [ __ ] it's not that it doesn't happen to me there are
chupar pollas no es que no me pasa hay
people who confuse not attacking with sucking
gente que confunde no atacar con chupar
[ __ ] okay but the moment
pollas vale pero ya en el momento que
turbo plan is using these
turbo plan está utilizando estos
arguments I no longer feel like
argumentos ya mí no me dan ganas de
arguing with turbo plan and debating anything
rebatir con turbo plan y de debatir nada
with turbo plan I even feel like
con turbo plan me dan ganas incluso de
letting him continue trusting what is known that
dejarle seguir fiando lo conocido
I do that river I do that
que eso yo sí lo hago río yo hago eso
suck [ __ ] river
chupar [__] río
I go to people to tell them there your clothes
yo voy a la gente a decirle hay tu ropa
in the best yesterday was the best making
en la mejor ayer es el mejor haciendo
videos airs I don't know what there is
vídeos aires no sé qué
download the dead of one but if
descargar los muertos de uno pero si
it's you we accept it
eres tú lo aceptamos
where do I do those rivers you can upload
donde hago yo esos ríos puedes subir me
explain it to me
lo explica
because honestly when I see this it reminds me
pues sinceramente yo cuando vea esto me
of villena of that river but that is what I
de villena de ese río pero el que es lo
do / river I should be able to upload in
que hago / río debía poder subir en
call
llamada
river you can upload in call
río puedes subir en llamada
because for me a message every 2 minutes is
porque a mí un mensaje cada 2 minutos no
useless to me upload call to the river
me sirve suben llamada al río
you can upload river
puedes subir río
now continue again you can't imagine the
ahora sigue otra vez no imagináis el
emptiness river you can upload
vació río puedes subir
river
río
typical hater of living
típico hater de vivir
that  I know that I am informed of the affairs
que yo sepa yo informado de los asuntos
of the vine and just like everyone else you can go up there
de vid y igual que de todos río puedes
was control a while ago he started
había control hace un rato se puso a
saying that ahead was a porn page
decir que adelante era una página porno
but that's what I'm telling you when you
pero es lo que te digo yo ya cuando
use these arguments turbo plan of
utilizas estos argumentos turbo plan de
disrespecting us to whoever thanks thank you
faltarnos el respeto a quien sea
very much
gracias muchas gracias
I'm going to use it
yo voy a utilizar
seems very childish it
me parece muy infantil
seems very childish of suck the [ __ ]
me parece muy infantil de chupa la [__]
to whoever had a go at the [ __ ] but
a quien le echó para la [__] pero que
still look at him even if he sucked his
igualmente mira aunque le chupara la
[ __ ] 15a you
[__] 15a
're not doing it he has no reason to
no lo estás haciendo no tiene por qué
insult anyone turbo I
insultar a nadie turbo
told him if he comes up tell me you said
le dije que si venga arriba dime tú dijo
river
río
river the methodical
río la metódico
river give me your discchord
río dame tu dischord
river come on we don't have all night
río vamos no tenemos toda la noche
give him service
dale servicio
air in get air in get
aire en [__] aire en [__] discos de
river discs when he feels like putting it on
río cuando le apetezca ponerlo
while we finish he treated him very badly
mientras que terminamos le trató muy mal
turbo plan the truth is not an argument at
turbo plan la verdad no es argumento de
all call suck support your partner
nada llama chupa apoya a tu compañero
because analyze things a little that is
porque analizar un poquito las cosas que
what this channel is about not
es de lo que trata este canal no de
trying to do a little things and
intentar realizar un poquito las cosas y
investigate a little not comment on the
de investigar un poco no de comentar los
salseros and that's it as it was
salseros por encima y ya está como era
of what he said not something assured plan
de lo que ha dicho no algo aseguró plan
but of a man of suck support I know
pero de un hombre de chupa apoya conozco
a few  but who are we
unos cuantos pero de quién estamos
talking about comment me well end
hablando comenta me bueno termina
end because if I felt like it
termina porque si me diera la gana
I would go and upload a video a day
cogería y subiría un vídeo por día
commenting on the salsa singers that are there reading
comentando los salseros que hay leyendo
the news reading four
las noticias por encima leyendo cuatro
tweets how do you guys do it and that's it
tweets cómo hacéis vosotros y ya está
but I don't do it because I like my
pero no lo hago porque me gusta que mis
videos to be a little more elaborate if it
vídeos sean un poquito más currado si me
touches my morals a little bit tell me
toca un poco la moral que me digáis a
biker very formed what some
biker muy formó lo que hacen algunos
youtubers do of salt I know or literally it
youtubers de sal se o literalmente
should be classified as
debería estar calificado como acoso
sexual harassment of the life of eggs that
sexual de la la vida de huevos que les
some youtubers do to them slam in no what
hacen algunos youtubers slam en no lo
the whole issue is no despite the fact
que viene siendo todo el tema no a pesar
that they [ __ ] and it's holding back their
de que cojan y está frenando sus
followers whether you see it for this I
seguidores ya sea lo veis por esto yo
think he's referring to cake you
creo que se refiere de tarta
can read my messages I said
se puede leer mis mensajes dije que por
please stop beating me tomorrow no no no
favor me dejaras de batir mañana no no
nothing tomorrow I'll be here for you
no nada mañana estaré aquí para ti
tomorrow with frank come on come on tell me tell me
mañana con frank vamos
your album please
vamos dime dime tu disco por favor
stop making excuses tomorrow nor tomorrow give me
déjate de escusas mañana ni mañana dame
your album
tu disco
I imagine that it stands out because he's
me imagino que se destaca porque se está
referring to me speaking well of d
refiriendo a que hable bien de d
of this despite the fact that this faith and it's like
de este a pesar de que esta fe y es como
I haven't spoken well of silver and the
yo no he hablado bien de silver y el
another one I ca
otro tampoco
n't see it hayden saga captures me do
no puedo verlo hayden saga me captura
you understand me
me entendéis
because he was the scammer or
ya porque haya sido él el estafador o
because he trusted him and was as
porque se haya fiado él y haya sido tan
irresponsible as promoting a
irresponsable como promocionar una
scam to his followers but oh well
estafa a sus seguidores pero bueno dios
my god what adif a no wait this I've already
mío lo que adif a no espérate esto ya lo
said before allow me small
he dicho antes permite mente pequeña
appreciation turbo popcorn but it's that
apreciación turbo pochoclo pero es que
since someone has sucked
ya que alguien la ha chupado la [__]
silvera's [ __ ] despite having scammed his
silvera a pesar de que haya estafado sus
followers
seguidores
I don't see that anyone has applauded
yo no veo que nadie haya aplaudido a
silver he hasn't seen the videos the
silver él no ha visto los vídeos lo
best thing is cakes some I don't know but it's
mejor es tartas algunos no lo sé pero
still to turn blanc who will
sigue siendo to turn blanc quien se
refer to it I think if they already get to the
referirá yo creo que si ya llegan al
act we are talking about sexual abuse not
acto estamos hablando de abuso sexual no
harassment but removing that perfect
de acoso pero quitando eso perfecto
throwing billy venting tea if I like to
tirando billy desahogando tea si me
say put myself in the comments
gusta decir ponerme en los comentarios
of who the [ __ ] do you think is talking because I
de quién [__] crees que habla porque yo
have no idea I am totally
no tengo ni idea yo quedo totalmente
free of sin since point number
libre de pecado puesto que punto número
one I have not commented on the subject and point
uno no he opinado del tema y punto
number 2 obviously I do not do direct let's
número 2 evidentemente no hago directo a
see what the south has said
ver qué ha dicho el sur
I am going to make you honest
yo voy a hacer honestos
I am going to make you honest for you
yo os voy a hacer honestos para vos
the river come now for  please
el río venga ya por favor
come please
yo venga por favor
rivers tell us your album please we do
ríos dinos tu disco por favor
n't have all night
no tenemos toda la noche
I think
yo creo
today try to change the
hoy intenta cambiar el perfil de
'twitter' profile
'twitter'
lamentable hayden non-fungible
lamentable hayden no fungible
lamentable lamentable shameful shameful
lamentable
lamentable
lamentable
you are right about seeing tweets in
tiene razón con lo de que ven tweets en
a live and what is the problem with seeing
un directo y cuál es el problema de ver
tweets in a live I mean it
tweets en un directo quiero decir
depends on what you want to do what is the
depende lo que quieras hacer cuál es la
legal where is the problem with seeing
legal dónde está el problema de ver
tweets in a live
tweets en un directo
you can get into a mess those who
tú te puedes meter en camisa de once los
lack respect turbo plan
que les faltan la respeta turbo plan a
despite the edge being missing with this
pesar de que el filo falte con este
institute and that is me seeing the
instituto y esa yo es que lo vea el
turbo plan
turbo plan
and I have pressured him for years that I
y le tengo a presiones por los años que
later did not go in hand but how
luego no fui de manos pero cómo
[Music]
[Música]
respect
el respeto
are the arguments he uses and the
son los argumentos que usa y las
conclusions he draws because they are not very
conclusiones que sacan porque no son muy
far
allá
because you do not mind with this
porque tú no te mente con este
guy and make a video about the
de varas y hacer un vídeo sobre la
silver scam and in the first video
estafa de silver y en un primer vídeo
call him a scammer and end up making
llamarle estafador y terminar haciendo
a second video rectifying that
un segundo vídeo rectificando eso
after having called him a scammer on more than
después de haberle llamado en más de
five or six occasions and
cinco o seis ocasiones estafador y
after insinuating the other ten and
después de insinuar la otras diez y
men and getting informed is making
hombres y informarse es hacer un primer
such a lamentable first video  that I have to do
vídeo tan lamentable que me toca hacer
a few seconds collecting cable because
unos segundos recogiendo cable pues
man I prefer to read tweets and not
hombre yo prefiero leer tweets y no
have to regret it and make a
tener que arrepentirme y hacer un
second video
segundo vídeo pidiendo disculpas
practically apologizing because of the
prácticamente pues por los vídeos de
previously banned videos that I've made you know what I
prohibida anterior que he hecho sabes lo
want to tell you video for that I
que te quiero decir vídeo para eso
prefer not to get information I prefer to continue
prefiero no informarme prefiero seguir
reading four tweets
leyendo cuatro tweets
to assume things that I can't assume
a asumir cosas que no puedo asumir saben
you know the river has risen that once
yo el río ha subido que pasado
the river has passed it's going to rise ok
el río se va a subir ok
and if you're going to read me read me completely but I
y si me vas a leer léeme completo pero
don't feel like it I don't
que no me apetece
feel like
no me apetece
waking up my father who's trying
despertar a mi padre que está intentando
just for a point comment that
sólo por un punto comentario que ni
wasn't even a joke they don't arrive they just
siquiera era una bromita no arriban
passed here the screen with
acaban de pasar aquí la pantalla con
all the comments posted on this
todos los comentarios a puestos en este
channel dude turn up wake your father
canal tío sube despertar a tu padre que
if you're watching a live tweet
si estás viendo un directo de tweet
directing and yelling turn up turn up
dirigir y gritando sube
if you put nonsense up I do
sube si pones tontería sube
n't feel like it because I'm not going to wake up
no me apetece porque no voy a despertar
my father
a mi padre
what town is
qué pueblo s
left is going to rise
queda va a subir
because you throw sports honey well this
porque tiras mieles deportivas pues este
is the type of audience that
es el tipo de público que le gusta a los
channels like plans like and that has told me they
canales como planos y que me ha dicho lo
support it you told
apoyan
me that I'm a [ __ ]
me has dicho que yo soy un chupa [__]
why because I do it  with beat and that I
por qué porque lo hago con beat y que yo
sucked him supports video
le chupó la apoya vídeo
that I support him because I tell him I
que yo lo apoyo porque le digo yo
told him something good I tell him of
le decía algo bueno se lo digo por
course not
supuesto no
these are the type of people that I don't want
estos son el tipo de gente que no quiero
here you understand
ya aquí entendéis
these are the type of people that I
estos son el tipo de gente que nos
love us and here that's why I contain myself
quiero y aquí por eso yo me contenido
now it is done in another way and also
ahora se hace de otra manera y además
you know that you can handle it and of
sabéis que ya lo podéis maneara y de
course it
jarrio
is as it is not only that the
esté como está no solamente que la
way is that the comments that they
manera es que la comentarios que ellos
see my youtube channels and youtube
vean mis canales de youtube y de youtube
if I were like this with pompn banned
si estuviera así con pompón baneado
just like the one like the same as
igual que el que al igual que igual que
the one that people before that is put
el que la gente antes que está puesto
enjoy Joan Plana when Joan has
disfrutar joan plana cuando joan ha
put the lock and it is not necessary
puesto el candado y no hace falta
or rather what there is is what there is
o sea lo que hay es lo que hay
God knows what looks to get into
sabe dios que mira para meterme en
places where I'm going to make a fool of myself
sitios donde voy a hacer el ridículo
well I don't get involved I don't get involved that's what there is
pues no me meto no me meto ya está lo
but apart from the argument now
pero es que aparte ya el argumento ahora
that he has uploaded another video
que ha subido otro vídeo
the argument is insulting the
ya el argumento es insultando a los
companions llosa
compañeros llosa
who ends up talking about the
que acaba hablando
same subject
del mismo tema
this red wine that steals mister bean and scams
este tinto que roba mister bean y estafa
but what is what I tell you that it does not
pero que es lo que te digo que no me
seem sensible to me the forms time and look
parece sentido las formas tiempo y mira
here of of  youtube
aquí de de youtube
[Music]
[Música]
and those things that I don't like these
y esas cosas que no me gustan estas
things these things I don't like the debate
cosas estas cosas no me gusta el debate
argue well there well look I prefer to
argumenta pues ahí pues mira yo prefiero
make my videos like this although
hacer mis vídeos así aunque se me vienen
the reflection of the glasses comes to me then the
el reflejo de las gafas luego las cosas
super things phrase my video so you
súper frase mi vídeo así que tú en
live because you live you make
directo porque tú en directo te
mistakes and you don't know how to
equivocas y no sabe
vocalize and pronounce the s very badly
vocalizar y pronunciar muy mal la s
erentxun so you don't mess with the
erentxun para que no te mete con los
youtubers big because you are a
youtubers grande porque eres un chupa
[ __ ] like me I already had my time of
[__] como yo ya tenía mi época de
messing with everyone and we don't mince words I
meterme con todo el mundo y no tenemos
mean the
pelos en la lengua es decir la
coincidence now I can tell you the same
casualidad ahora puedo decirte lo mismo
without disrespecting you I leave you the same and I do
sin faltarle al respeto te dejo igual y
n't get into any trouble and maybe
no me meto ningún lío y a lo mejor ganó
now I earn triple or four times the money
ahora el triple o cuatro veces el dinero
that you earned and even I am interested in
que ganaban te y hasta de me interesa
living more and I am interested in more more I lived
más vivías y me interesa más más vivía
without more calm more money and with
sin más tranquilos más dinero y con
less heat headache maybe it's
menos calor quebradero de cabeza a lo
not about [ __ ] the best thing is for me to
mejor no es de chupa [__] lo mejor es
be a little more intelligent
que sea un poco más inteligente
today is the day
hoy es el día
no
no
[Music]
[Música]